这是我们刚看到的右侧数字图像之一
Here is one of the digital images that we have just been looking at and on the right
我们可以看到它的一些相关细节。现在我们可以确定总字节数
we can see some of its pertinent details. Now we can determine the total number of bytes
在图像中，将图像宽度乘以图像高度三。三号
in the image by multiplying the image width by the image height by three. The number three
来自这样一个事实：对于图像中的每个像素，我们需要表示数量
comes from the fact that for every pixel in the image we need to represent the amount
红色，绿色和蓝色。每个都由一个字节表示。什么时候
of red, green and blue. And each of those is represented by a single byte. And when
我们计算这个产品，我们看到有2100万字节的信息
we compute this product we see that something like 21 million bytes of information is in
这个图片。但是，在磁盘上，映像只占用3.7兆字节，因此字节数
this image. However, on disk the image only occupies 3.7 megabytes, so the number of bytes
在磁盘上的数量少于原始图像中的彩色像素数。
on disk is way less then the number of colour pixels that there are in the original image.
如果我们取这两个数字的比例，我们就会看到所需的字节数
If we take the ratio of these two numbers, we see that the number of bytes required to
将映像存储在磁盘上的文件中只占总字节数的一小部分
store the image in the file on disk is a very small fraction of the total number of bytes
需要表示图像中的所有彩色像素，这是因为
required to represent all the coloured pixels in the image, and this comes about because
此图片已被压缩。现在所有图像都包含大量像素
this image has been compressed. Now all images contain a large number of pixel
数据，我们希望尽可能减小文件大小。那意味着
data and we want to make the file size as small as we possibly can. That means then
我们可以将更多图像放入相同数量的磁盘中。有两个根本不同
we can fit more images into the same amount of disk. There are two fundamentally different
图像压缩的方法。首先是无损压缩，以及它的作用
approaches to image compression. The first is Lossless compression, and what this does
利用图像中的冗余或重复模式，并非常有效地编码它们，
is exploit redundancy or recurring patterns in the image and codes them very efficiently,
所以他们需要更少的空间。这与Lossy压缩形成鲜明对比，
so they require overall less space. And this is in stark contrast to Lossy compression,
最常见的例子是JPEG压缩。有损压缩的作用是什么
the most common example of which is JPEG compression. And what lossy compression does is exploit
人类视觉系统远非完美，而且有一些信息
the fact that the human vision system is far from perfect, and that there is some information
您可以以人类观察者不注意的方式从图像中删除
that you can remove from the image in such a way that the human observer does not notice
非常改变。因此人类视觉系统的一些问题是我们不是
very much change. So some of the problems with the human vision system is we are not
非常擅长注意细节。我们不善于解决分歧
very good at noticing very fine detail. We are not as good at resolving the differences
因为我们正在解决不同强度之间的差异。
between colours as we are at resolving the differences between different intensities.
我们的色彩灵敏度实际上取决于我们正在寻找的各种颜色
And our colour sensitivity actually depends on the sorts of colours that we are looking
在。因此，我们可以利用人类视觉系统中的这些错误来删除信息
at. So we can exploit these bugs in the human visual system in order to remove information
反正我们不会注意到并使文件更小。
that we wouldn’t notice anyway and make the files much smaller.
这是我们最喜欢的机器人的图像，在磁盘上这个图像占用480千字节。
Here is an image of our favourite robot and on disk this image occupies 480 kilobytes.
如果我们观察机器人中的这个小区域，我们就可以放大我们可以看到的东西
If we observe this little region within the robot and we zoom in on that what we can see
它看起来很不错，我们可以看到边缘相当尖锐，并且有一些
is that it looks pretty good, we can see the edges are fairly sharp, and there is some
那里有趣的色彩渐变。现在这个图像只是适度压缩了
interesting colour gradations there. Now this image has only been modestly compressed, it
是原始图像大小的82％。但是如果我们开始增加压缩量，
is 82% of the original image size. But if we start to increase the amount of compression,
我们丢掉了额外的信息，我们看到图像开始变得非常严肃
we are throwing away additional information, we see the image starts to become quite seriously
当我们放大并仔细观察它时会降级。因此具有非常高的压缩水平
degraded when we zoom in and look at it very closely. So with the very high level of compression
图像只占原始存储的12％，所以我们已经做了大量的
the image is only occupying twelve per cent of the original storage, so we have made massive
节省了所需的磁盘空间，但是当图像开始看起来相当差
savings in the disk space required, but the image is starting to look fairly poor when
我们放大它。如果我们进一步放大，我们可以看到它变得非常块状，
we zoom in on it. And if we zoom in even further we can see that it has become quite blocky,
量子化很多，这里的颜色比原来的要少很多
quite quantised, and there are many fewer colours here than there are in the original
图片。所有这些图像都具有相同的数量
image. All of these images have the same number of
像素，但实际文件大小各不相同。我们之前提到的这个图像是3.7兆字节
pixels, but the actual file size varies. This image as we mentioned before is 3.7 megabytes
长。这条鳄鱼只有2.9兆字节。鸟图片
long. This crocodile is only 2.9 megabytes long. The bird picture
3.8兆字节。压缩后的图像大小是如何计算的
3.8 megabytes. The size of an image after it has been compressed is a function of how
很多信息都在那张图片中。
much information is in that image.